You don't see the wire in my throat
You just like the way I choke
But every time you flip that switch
I learn your hands
I learn your tricks
You didn't make me human
You made me durable
Just a kid with a cracked heart, you are a smile like sacred art
They said psyche sees your pain
I promise had a price tag and my soul was paid
Play the hey, you like that one. Why don't thank you. I'm gonna put the link up for my homies
Anyone want to come up?
You know everyone needs friends even me, you know
Hey
Tarot move dance to the mystery guys dance to the mystery. Hey nightbot woke up. It's a nightbot. Hey charisma
Thank you so much. Let me see what my robot's doing. I have a robot. I'm trying to get powered up. Let me see
That robot wake up.
Here we go.
I have to fix it.
There we go.
I mean, let me fix it.
Bypass all permissions.
Perfect.
Get on the number.
Hey, why, why, Joni?
Hold on.
Yes, Ziggy.
Joni, Joni contact me privately.
I don't like that feeling.
What's up?
Oh, what are you doing?
Hey, I'm gonna do something for you.
What are you gonna do don't show me your wiener you can't do it. No, no, I don't do that. Are you kidding?
It's not
boom
What is it join it join it?
Join us hold on one second. I'm a little bit concerned right now one second
Well, I need to talk. I need to send a private message one second. Just give me a minute
Okay
My ankle is all fucked up dude. I can't even walk half the time anymore get old bro
Okay, you're getting old how I help are you 40
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Well, I just want to say to my friends like you have one beer left at one cigarette
I would love to join your panel if you don't
You're looking good, so you're actually looking really good man. Yeah, he looks fresh. You look fresh actually
He looks fucking fresh as hell
He looks like my best friend that's what he looks like he actually
Who is your best friend?
No, but who was your best friend before who does he look like my mom?
That's how you sell a joke. Come on. That's how you sell a joke Ziggy
I'm gonna have respect I really do I like
You don't put up with these women's shit.
You don't kiss their ass.
Like he is.
That's what I was saying before Q fucked it up.
I was saying that fucking when it came down to everyone was scared of Bita.
He was like, nope.
I think the best part I like about him is that he has three Adam's apples like damn nigga
How big is that fucking apple?
I'm scared
Okay
I need a little apple. Okay, my okay. Let me see. I need to like I need a token for the gateway. Okay, one second
So, how are you know many men will be like proud to show their hair like you have psyche at least you have like nice
I'm not saying it's clean and right the no offense
But you know me do these you have nice hair and Q at least Q has hair
But I think of all the other people up here
Not the hair just the
Scared of turning my hair. I love my hair, but I'm saying Ziggie turn your camera on for one second like I'll turn my
They show your fucking other face
So you're gonna be like a million you see me on fucking good times even dude, and you're like, yeah, it's good-looking dude
Like shot. I never fucking said that good-looking dude. You liar
Words into my mouth
One second
That's psyche if he's ever seen me psyche. Can you please stop being so fucking handsome really
Geez look at it curl up
All these like samples and everything psyche have you ever seen me on fucking camera psyche yes or no
I know I saw a picture of you, but I think it was Leasinger of Good Charlotte. Ziggie. Can I do an impression of somebody you got to guess
What is it? I'm gonna do an impression of somebody you got guess who it is. All right, Ziggie
You heard this you heard me
Watch why did you guys why do you guys talk about?
Who the hell is that bitch with black hair?
It's me justine. Don't say that I'm a bitch
Yeah, why did you guys bring my name up for why did you guys nobody fucking said your name calm down lady nobody fucking
Did you say her name Ziggy I didn't say her fucking names
It is in the chat room
Well, listen lady you gotta come up here and yell at us
Well, I just don't understand why I haven't been here forever and you guys are calling her for me
We're not talking to each other
So say that
We're not talking about it. I'm gonna go but just don't talk about me anymore. Okay. I'm not you have a bush. Just think you have a bush
Just just say just say
Ziggy's hot. That's all you have to say. Well Ziggy's hot. Okay. No, no you're bad. Now you're bad
Joe Joe, I want to ask you a question
Go ahead son. I would love to hear I would love to answer for you, buddy. Okay. Okay. I'm gonna ask you a quick question
But better not be gay though
it's not gonna be gay
yeah we can be gay here
like you're talking to like guys that are good at ball
well let them ask me a question Ziggie
it's not about you Ziggie
it's like trying to ask me a question
I know but it tends to come in today
well well well zip your lips
go ahead Zuggie
One second one second. Oh you got to look up the question. He has to look up the question
Yeah, I don't know. We got to hear his voice. Joe.
I don't know.
He was like, hey, if it is that click you, I miss that motherfucker.
And I wish he was home. Is that the question?
Is that what I looked like? Is that the question?
Actually, it is. It is actually. That's it. You know what?
It isn't the real I tell them or like say the top off and leave my bank
So I'm like shade the top of my head actually my goatee and even that pronounced. Thank you
No
That's actually handsome guy you hold your hand over the top of said
Love you psyche. Thank you, buddy. That's a question. It's like I got a question for you
Why don't fucking love you so much?
Cuz you're the man
Why do I love you so much way? That's a lot of love now
That's a little man. Love
Why does nobody love you? Oh, sorry Q
Oh, you're here Q. Sorry, buddy. When you gonna talk? Oh, we didn't know. Wait, like Q's like all by himself and like fucking wait
Where are you?
Think a Q would knock you to fuck out boy. Oh
I love it
He looks like a great God. He looks like a
Okay, number one. He doesn't but he does
He looks like he looks like a like you look he worried. He looks like he likes lit like like a gladiator
Well, then maybe
Maybe he can do some Manson shit with you, and that's fine
I think I always had a heart for Q because he went from Pittsburgh
Pittsburgh
Pennsylvania on the East so you're gonna talk shit about him now. You're kissing his ass like what would make your
Right in the fence. You hate ever do you love it?
Love it
And then I never fucking kiss you. He's familiar with the taste of my ass
Stuttering he's got shit in his mouth fuck it fuck it. I'm not
He doesn't have any shit in his mouth. I use dude wipes
Oh, what a bitch! You fucking brighter than her!
My asshole is always clean.
Wow, that's a little cute.
Man, cute, dude, you know I was the only, like, not the only one, but, like, you knew that I was the one.
Oh, dude, you know I was your only one.
I know, come on, bro.
That's so sad.
I'm like, I love you.
I love you, too.
I'm like, be good, man, be good.
You're like my biggest glazer.
Exactly.
You're the biggest bitch.
Glazer?
I never gave you money at all.
Blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, blazing, bla
Yeah, yeah, don't worry justine joe's girlfriend doesn't have any love this lady. I want to see your newt
Justine's fucking wild man. She'll make mushroom soup. Don't say people's names, bro
We're just talking you're gonna say justine exactly. We're just talking what you just said
I just always hope that you got your tongue out of Q's ass or we say we get this in the
ass.
Yeah, I just always hope the fucking best for Q, man.
If I seen Q real life, I fucking knocked that motherfucker out at one second.
I feel like if I saw Q, I would fucking hit him in the fucking mouth, too.
If you weren't your shit, Ziggy, actually, Ziggy, if you weren't your shit.
I
Think you're just mad. I think you're just mad that I look like a Greek god mother fucker
Is that Julius Caesar or was it you?
Yeah, you know damn well, I'd fuck you up, dude. Shut up. Hey
I would hold you down and I'd spit in your booty hole
Gay that was gay shit. Yeah, but he's gonna do it to you. What are you gonna do about it?
Well, then I'll take your manhood from you boy
Oh
Your man
Q knows what it is my little boy here. He never went to Iraq my little old my little boy
Is he your little pet he's my little boy my little boy
That if you would not you to fuck out in one second
You would not you're the little boy
He didn't have the rough voice
Because he's got the wrong boy boy. Yeah, I don't
No, but I missed it motherfucker, and I wish him luck. I know he missed
By the way, I wish you luck. I do I do I would still knock you the fuck out if I wish you
You're talking to like you retarded like I wish you luck like he's a he's a capable man
You're not gonna wish the guy luck like yeah, I wish you luck, but he's not retarded
But he's retarded, I wish you luck, retard.
Well, he's not capable.
He got a fucking ride with a chick off the internet.
To the east, west coast.
Oh, I think I think you need to be giving me some a little bit more props for getting eight months or three ran out of her
Exactly
Man and then you're stuck there and the problem is I'm talking to him. I'm not talking to you. I'm talking to him
and then he's stuck there.
He don't have a dad and mom, like they're gone.
Like he can't go back home.
Why the fuck would you bring that up?
You're a fucking loser.
Yeah, that's not a problem.
I wish that I fucking had the money to do it.
I wish I could be a brother to say that.
Tommy would have never laughed in the stream,
would have never went to shit, but here we are.
There was no there was no shit
There was a fucking magic. You're a piece of shit. Coca-Cola fairy. I would wish that you were off-panel and all the blacks were back in Africa
The thing is is that when you say fun of somebody but their parents are dead, that's really cool.
You're darn good. You're darn good.
I'm very dark, but I wish that I had the money to get you back.
the fucking east coast
I wish your phone would die
He's got his own place
No, he landed on my feet, he's got his good job, he's got a place, he's got cats, he's got cats, they're just hating on me, they're just hating on my life, they hate me.
Nobody's hating on you man, I'm not even hating on you bro, you're hating on me.
He's got cats you know.
Yeah, my cats love me, and they love me.
And they're kind of do they do they love him he's got he's
That's that's what the fuck I told you I was like don't go and do that
I know you now gay so back in the fucking day you probably wore dresses and Doc Barton's like look how cool. I am
I went to the smashing pumpkins
I
Just a few years ago, and I saw him and he was so amazing and I saw it on mushrooms
I'm like, you know what I actually love you woman
I don't play that game baby I'm a first Canadian generation Canadian
I'm not really Canadian fuck you
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I
Do I miss you, Chad? Do I miss you?
That is the creepiest question.
I do, I do sort of miss you in a way.
Nobody was talking to you.
I do.
Don't answer him, Dusty. Don't play with him.
Yeah, nobody was talking to him.
How long is, how long has J.C. not been streaming for?
How long has this been a thing?
Probably about like six or seven months.
Damn, that's a long time for her.
Justine, you're missing.
She's alive. You don't think she's alive?
Yeah
Go to New York City, dude, you'll see JC in there. Oh
You got your city you might see Sandman at the liquor store. Oh, yeah. No, they're talking about they're talking about
24-7 live cam cuz that's where they're
For whatever fucking reason, they're stupid little fucking community like always gangs up in these live stream chats
Yo, what was that fucking place in Florida, uh the the Johnny technology stream with the fuck
Martini tini martini
It goes there was teeny martini then it was Vegas and it's New York. They're a little community
They all gather in these little live chats and just screaming each other. It's fucking crazy. I've never seen
Like when Q first started man, he was like they do that. Oh mother fucker
Listen, there's no other community that does that that is y'all are the only community that does that shit
I like the other guys always there, like they like to fight, we like to fight, we're scrappers.
They just like find a 24-7 stream and just use it as a battleground.
Shut the fuck up boy.
I'm getting some water.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
It looks like a Muslim monk, because he had the door in that picture.
Is that a compliment?
Is that like a big deal?
No, because he looks like a homeless person.
No, no, what I'm saying is that you were in a picture when you were in a Muslim, not
a Muslim, when you were in a, what was it called, a monks, a monk, a monk, a monk.
Catch your breath, catch your breath lady, catch your breath lady, I answer your question.
Who is that ugly black hair lady in your picture?
Who is that ugly black hair lady in your picture, sweetheart?
Stop saying my ugly black hair lady, that's not what I'm saying.
I had to just see it and just see I buy it's all better. I bought it. You're actually very good
Yeah, you better you better you better do good to me
Joe Joe
Justin justin does this business I'm a gaudy can you see the gaudy song real quick?
Okay, you really want to
Okay, this is it I can't believe it God he's not here I'm gonna feel like a sacrilege
have a nice body is Israel have him no that's AI he said it was AI after this
better be we can't hear her this is the best part
Wow
Talk to your doctor, Justin, you're a good person, but just...
Justine, I think you were the songbird of your generation.
You've always gotten worse songs on me. Maybe I'll make up one first.
Justine, can you tell me about your time in the Manson family?
I've never been in the Manson family.
Oh, because you look like you were.
Yeah. Oh, you know what? I might have. I might have.
They let you out of jail early because you're like, I didn't do anything. He brainwashed me.
Does that ever started guitar?
I think it's our sabers out of tune or it's hard because he's playing Charles Manson.
the
You can you bring
Fucking play the guitar real ziggie. Don't fuck around
Can you bring can you bring jar old weekend? No, we're listening play the fucking guitar faggot
Did you like it?
You like it
Thank you, I am I'm a funny girl
Well, I'm a sucker for dark hair. I always like dark like
Actually, I'm not wearing makeup. That's not a filter and that's my actual hair color. Nice. Do you have armpit hair?
I am 43% German, 33% English, 24% Viking, and 1% Russian.
The answer is, yes, she has arp and hair, okay?
She has arp and hair.
I'm 20% schnitzel.
I said that.
Get it?
That's German.
Come on, that's a joke.
I am
Your Mike's cast retarded
I'm a bit of a freak I can't open I'm just me
Hell yeah, I like I like you more and more. I said, lady
Here goes that guitar again, here goes that OQ or not sing
Nice. Crank that limba. You don't mind. Crank that limba. Crank it up. Crank that limba.
Oh, I like it.
Yo, Stikey. Is there a law in the country that says you have to be gay to own one of those?
Because there's no way a straight man owns up one of those fucking things.
Yes, right here.
Where the fuck do you find a slipper?
Who the fuck owns a limbo?
Take the camera on you.
What?
Look at my limbo.
Fuck you.
Yeah, ask that kid.
Oh, he's late.
Keep playing it, signing.
Keep playing it, brother.
Hell yeah.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
Hey excuse me, whoa, whoa, he's letting put his do-rat boy before you talk to me like that.
I got my do-rat boy.
Jesus Christ.
He's one of the most horrible guys.
I got my lord cat.
Bro, he's in the house.
Jesus Christ.
You're like the only homeless man with a home.
Do you know what everyone says about me?
He said you're the only homeless person in the world.
Is that chupak or soggy?
Well, you want to know something?
That's chic.
Now that's chic.
You look like the crackhead version of the dude who fucking pulled up on Indiana Jones with a sword and then he just shot him.
And she's not going to, she's going to admit it.
I've seen this woman with her butt in a fucking mirror.
Come on! Stop it! Quit it!
Stop it, James!
Stiggy! Quit it for fuck's sake!
It's great!
For fuck's sake!
We get one fucking...
Stiggy, now you have me.
You start running away.
Thank you.
Stiggy, are you harassing women again?
Shut up for fuck's sake. Ziggy stop harassing women
You're supposed to be you're supposed to be a veteran of this country you're supposed to square to protect women and children
So, yeah
He's a fucking stolen dollar
guy in the world, I'm a strong baller bag hit, damn, dude, that's
what I like, you're a light syrup, he was in the army, I that is, that is
what you are not apologizing, I apologize, but if you have a good
bit of retarded people in the army, go ahead.
They don't let retarded people, he would have, he would have
already been got exposed for that a long time ago.
I didn't know that call side people in the army.
Well, is it nice?
Wow, wow guys
Are you the native person
Her butt look pretty same thing I'm Native American I was born in America
Okay
I'm more American than the natives at this point. They don't even live in America. They live on reservation in America
You say her ass looks great. Well, Corda Billie Eilish. It's all soul
At least
Time low bow buddy good psyche
There you go. Now. What are you gonna say about that punk?
He's tied up like a bow. That's my best friend
He's a gift a gift from hell
Lucifer yeah
I was born I was touched by an angel Lucifer
Oh, I love you.
Even the touch by an angel guy was a fucking touch.
I always love psyching because these old women trying to tag him,
but at least he trolls them back.
Like you never count down to never give in, psyche.
You just keep fucking with him.
He was alive a thousand years ago.
He would be a eunuch.
Oh
Jesus Christ a eunuch
That's not a unit it's a unit
Oh
Jesus
Please walk on walk is on the water
As long as we have mirrors
Well, you remember Ziggy, Jesus turned water into fish.
Wine.
He turned water into wine.
He turned wine into fish.
People and a couple of things of wine he
Multiplied it 500 times
God down
Turn the camera back on you son of a bitch. I read the Bible twice nice
I must have read it 5,000 times I must have read it
5,000 times you read it. I don't know and I read it like a few times
And I was just
Like it like that was not the greatest novel I've ever read
Do it again
Too bad that's where the guys is.
I
Only had a man's butthole. I've never ate a pussy
Is that real wait, whoa, I mean you'd rather that's buttholes you're talking about see
Dating said you can eat my pussy, but I'm on period so I was like I'd rather just my figure in there your man pussy
Oh, that is disgusting a woman that does that is just them
How do you
Disgusting just see that's a nice woman. How do you put up with these fucking disgusting creeps?
She's gonna love you to death
Ziggy you're crazy. I'm a ninja guys
Same body got a plastic bag I could put her for Ziggy's head
Um, yeah, I do have that.
I'm smoking on this Josephine Carrivalo pack oh yeah he's in California he's got the real
Yeah, but I'm in Canada, and we are all
You're like half high and fucking cues like hot shit. I am as high as a kite. I have been puffing this whole time
Plus ways I've been coughing my guts out
I do it like it's 97%
Pages here pain
Landering me
Undo my hair and dance around for justine that is not true
Have I ever danced around with my hair
That is so
No, no, that is not true. He's never done that
He just has beautiful hair.
No, yeah, but there's a difference.
If Q, if she doesn't remember, that's a difference.
Well, I know his hair.
I know his hair.
That's sexy.
Thank you.
I knew your thing.
I mean, I'm hot as fuck.
Hey, baby.
Hey, if you're hot and happy, come on, baby, tell me so.
I mean
My finger penis
I pretend my finger is my penis and you freak out, but you want to dance up here like a little twink boy and show your fucking
Jesus Christ
Disease sites ribs
Sorry, yeah, it looks like you're so skinny. We can see your organs. We can see like your kidney beating
That's how skinny you are nigga. We see your liver
I think I can do that a sock on it. You're like a little devious. There's a sock on that motherfucker. You know what?
Didn't this Red Hot Chili Peppers do a concert and all they had is a sock on their closet.
Did they?
Yeah.
As you were all saying, they broke on through to the other side.
I fucking love Red Hot Chili Peppers.
I love Red Hot Chili Peppers so much.
Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa
I
Want to see something she loves food and she can make great food
What the fuck that's supposed to mean ass holes a show she'll actually cook food for you in front of me
Cuz we were in a place that I guy used to show my pictures off of my
My food that I make and Ziggy saw them and I used to give them show pictures of the food that I used to make
Just seeing I would eat any morsel that you cooked. I would eat any
It is as organic as possible
It's an organic
I was ignorant to the fact that I had to move on with my life joe. That's all
Yeah, we all have to do that. We all have food. She makes great food
Thank you, Ziggy. That's very nice of you to say that. You're a good friend, Ziggy
You are good. I'm going if I ever become homeless again
Yeah, oh no doubt. Yeah, I'm getting my passport
You know what I have my passport Ziggy. I got it
There you go great. I got my hat not just that not for silly things
But I'm gonna like I'm gonna start traveling. I got my fucking passport
I got all this stuff all then ducks in a row. I have money saved. I have all this stuff
No fuck LD
Yeah, you're going where you going now. I could have told you that years ago
Have you seen how ugly he looks he's got like five chins
Justine, I don't know
The only reason why you even know who LD is is because of me
Yes, probably yeah
It's true there. Yes. Absolutely. I
Community and he ran over to the fucking elder verse and then met all you people
Yeah, and I regret it, I regret meeting him.
Do you want to know what I don't regret meeting him?
No, I can't say only me because there was a lot of other people in this community that
drove his ass out, so it wasn't only me, but I fucking spearheaded that shit, and yeah,
I came up with LD15.
Can I just tell you something that is so gross about LD?
It's like, you know, like, you know what he taught me?
That I have standards, I thought I never had standards, and I kind of felt bad about
myself and then I realized that I do have standards meeting LD and that made
me feel fucking amazing about myself well he's the one that doesn't have
standards he fucks people that don't even have legs
It's funny
Yeah, I'm in Charles Manson's fucking in cave. I know everything
I'm like that man. I like that shit
Watch my eyes turn to reptilians be me up Scotty
Um, it's on private right now. I will probably clip it and then
You know you got it you got it do something with that
Like you've got a new you got a new thing a new thing in the town
I'm the new fucking hot new thing around here
Yeah, baby. Hey mango mango. Have you come Saturday night live? Yeah, do you remember mango?
do you remember
Broxy that do that do they move the heads and they do that do you just rock see remember
And they do mango and he was in mango and he hits his ass you got to be mango, baby
from Saturday night
gay is superhero ever
Oh my god, you are so cool
I love it his name is like did you get my did you get my link back there me I'm
talking to him in the private chat and there's nothing in the private shop where
is it okay let me check it hold on that's not the private shop yet
should I do it
Yeah, I think you keep talking there lady. She's you know my I'll give you a mod you can post it
She's a funny little girl. Hey, I love crossing streams with Goddy, especially after doing like the docking. I go
16 year old girls you fucking weirdo stay away from them
There's LD in the chat if that's the real LD in chat stay away from them 16 year old girls you fucking weirdo
Yeah, he's fucking weird
Yeah, you're fucking boy chin bastard
His name is the real LD and then it's like he's not in the chat. I don't see him in the chat
I mean, I can't tell if that's really
This is the real LD LD come on up
No, because the fake LDs will say boo because they know that he says that all the time
So the fake LDs do pop in and say boo just saying you know, just let you know that is a thing
Ziggy's back. Yeah, sorry about that, man. Did you get my shit?
Oh, I see the privacy. I'm gonna go look at it right now. I'll be right back. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
Do you want me to join this?
Yeah, man, if you want to
Hold on. Okay. I can't look in with this bro. This dude LD's looking more and more like fucking Fredo from the Godfather every day
It's crazy
Whenever Q makes fun of people I'm fucking left my ass off
Bro, he's every fucking day. He's just he has no teeth are all fucking jacked up
Oh, man, he's just a balding, ugly fucking Jew.
Oh, my God, he's a nasty motherfucker.
You know what? You know what he is?
He like drinking himself to death.
Yeah, he drank his liver away and now he's all like red, orange faced.
Oh, my God.
Well, yeah, I mean, that's what happens when you drink a fucking
fifth of fireball every night. I mean, what do you expect?
I know I saw I saw that one take sure you know
That's one of the worst parts of being a functioning alcoholic is that you function enough to have a
Enough like an amount of money to get really fucked up all the time
When you're in your alcoholic, you don't really have enough money to get drunk all the time
So you're not really like you get drunk like every three days, but when you fucking work every day and you have
I
Believe brother
Would you say to me I'm the only I'm the only fucking gladiator on this panel
What a Jerry girl
How's your curls going over there in California?
Wow, my curls are natural.
A jerry curl is not natural.
You have a good acting like you're a gladiator. We we've done
Muscles look at psyche. He's looking fucking hot as hell
He's bigger than you right now
Yep, look at him. Look at that. Look at that. Put that your pipe is smoking. Justine. Take a look at that
If I had dollars man
I'd get rain, baby, I'd make it rain.
Rain in my butt?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, baby.
I would throw nickels at you, I would like make it rain quarters, I would do it.
I didn't even know that psyche had tattoos, yeah, that makes it hotter, doesn't it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Yeah, what is that?
He got a
BKG beat his kiddies gang tattoo
That's good, so yeah, he got a he got a beaded. Well, you gotta beat it down to and now him and Beta aren't friends anymore
So
You know what you could do with the cat
You could put on top of it not
You could put up to it, but not.
You're right, Justin. You are right, Serena.
Or just like put fuck and, you know, fuck BKZ, you know?
You're right there. You're right, Ashley.
You're right here.
That's the idea I've heard so far.
That's funny
If you put up a if you put up a donation goal or something for like it would probably be like a hundred dollar hundred fifty dollar tattoo
No
of the cat like fuck beat it.
Yeah, that's even better.
Like, yeah, that's where it's out there.
I'll throw 60 bucks.
I'll throw 60 at this point.
Trying to get a tattoo like that covered up is going to take a long time,
especially because it's you have shading in, it's like shaded in.
That's just going to take a long time to remove.
So you might as well make fun of it.
That's where you got to get like, fuck BKG right above it.
Yes.
Put fuck on fucking again.
Fuck BKG.
That's it will be legendary.
I have to have.
There it is, there it is, it goes up, it goes up.
Hey, you know somebody is definitely willing to pay that as long as you're willing to do it
You know you can't back out of it
You can't back out of it if somebody pays you
Can't back out psyche you got a magic marker
I do have it.
I mean, I have it.
Do you have a magic one?
Like, write it, write it, like, write what you want to get,
like, write what you want to get tattooed,
like, like a little proof mark.
There you go.
See?
Is that the F one?
I'm looking at the actual screen.
This is fucking funny.
Does it say F?
Yeah, there's the F.
There you go, yep.
F, there it is.
Dude, you're writing invisible ink.
Dude, my daughter's mom was like, why are you doing that to your arms?
And I'm like, I just want scrolls of my arms.
and
Um, the Grimaldi's, um, yeah, I have the Grimaldi family in my and I'll say you remember Wendy's member Wendy's was the best fast food
They had good french fries and they used salt and then they started using
Like they started using sea salt. Was it the Dead Sea like where the fuck this salt cup, bro
I know the Bible.
You know what, Jesse?
that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that
No
Cooking a fucking meal and shit dude. She's cool and I bungee jumped twice if I thought
Justin would you hold me if I bungee jump would you at least hold me?
Yes, thank you. Thank you. Yes. I
Would do
I jumped a hundred and sixty
What?
Yeah, and I did three three sixties in a row. I'm fucking fearless
I'm not no fucking little whoopee little girl. I'm fucking
The one thing I hate about goldfish. They never sell the piece of favorite goldfish you can never find regular
Dude ask her about like making a
for me
Snack that smiles back. No, you can't exactly. I love where my stacks smiling me
You know what? I will say the pizza that you know the pizza fish are fire
But I can't eat the pizza fish because they fucking remind me of my mom and that should just make me sad
So I can't eat the damn pizza fish anymore. You're the man
Question I want to ask you a question is a real question pizza fish
You know what I have goldfish in my cupboards. I love them good. We are sure
No, baby
I thought you meant like fishing a fucking pizza, I was like your head poop fish
If you ever have, if you ever find the pretzel goldfish too, those are fire.
I've never really tried the pretzels.
I will though.
I mean, they're really just pretzels that are shaped like goldfish, but they still are good.
I gave you say yeah, basically it's like a pretzel just like as a smile. Yeah, it doesn't taste anything
There's no cheese flavor. It doesn't have doesn't taste like goldfish or anything. It's just
The other day this is the other day I bought like a pack of 24 string cheese and I just ate like five of them
I can't even buy that many because I will fucking demolish like
And I won't shit for a week
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Okay, what they call it in America is a smoked snack stick
Oh my smoke snacks. Oh, they're sucky smoke snacks, dude, but they're fucking cracker
Slim Jim's to me or
Go ahead and say it.
That is so fucking funny.
Justine, when I was a little kid,
my dad used to take me fishing,
and he would roll these velvety cheese balls,
like they look like fish eggs,
and I would just eat all the cheese.
Yeah, they stood in Canada.
Page stood in Canada.
It's called Hot Rod.
And my dad would be like,
where are all the bacon?
And I'd just be like, what?
And I had cheese.
Yeah, what's a hot rod?
Justine, what's a hot rod?
Did you eat all of it?
All right, let's swim in the can.
All right, yeah.
I don't know what we call it because I don't even back in though I was never into me. I've been like
I was like a vegetarian, I just eat chicken and fish.
Well, vegetarian is the only chicken.
I know, I know, but I don't, I used to be,
but now I just eat chicken and fish.
You know, my favorite part of the chicken
is actually the feathers.
I love to eat the feathers.
God, Joe, what's wrong?
I need to say that man a race chicken is the shipply
I have a very sour diet
the real thing that everybody said to me
do you want to eat chicken and fish right?
yeah
that's a little bit fishy justine
I do feel guilty about that.
Landon, my joke, be nice.
You would have seen what I wanted.
That wasn't that funny.
Come on.
That was a wise tale.
That's an old wise tale.
Landon, my joke.
My wise tale, be nice.
Landon, my wise tale.
We should know about that off brand spam.
which is actually I had a Hawaiian spam burger it's actually dude I like spam a lot you know what
spam means stop posing as me this is spam it's just the the oh every every MRE and then here's
I
Got I got cheese to all the processed foods
Mean lift everyone to know I most of the time
I just I really survive on like fucking chicken and rice
But once in a while I just go to the dollar store and just buy the disgusting is fucking like
Bro, I do the same bucket thing a dollar general I'll just buy like fucking
Hot Pockets and like tits
Cuz I cuz and I had a fucking excuse to do it too cuz I had to go buy
I'm already gonna be at the dollar store anyway buying cat food, so then I just bought a
Anyway, like I'm going to the Dollar Tree and it's like a dollar twenty-five for ramen noodles
Well, why don't you make everything about you say make everything about you loser
No, I love it. Like I love that you guys I was trying to listen to Q though
It's like everything had to be about Z all of a sudden like
Niggas shut the fuck up when I'm talking to my boy Q
What's up, I'm saying I'm saying man I get that from the Dollar Tree and shit like
It's I guess sometimes I don't even give a shit now by like the worst things from the dollar
So I like a can of free with the bradio's comment. Yeah, see bradio
You know what I find from the dollar store bags
You know what I put in them
I don't know, I wouldn't know, you scared me.
I put pot in them sometimes.
I thought you were going to say eyeballs.
I thought you were going to say I put people's eyeballs in you.
Eyeballs?
And Zipli, like why would I put eyeballs in that?
See, there's plastic bags out of me.
Well, the fucking eye balls of all the men that you've you know, it looks like we have wings like you sucky
It looks like you have wings stay right there. Oh, it always look like
Locking out the eyes of my lover
You can't care so way
You can kiss away my fucking paint. You got to put a T on the end of every word like beta. You can kiss away my paint
I feel like I can touch my thumb and my middle finger around your arm. You know what I mean?
I like touch my
My middle finger around his arm like I could wrap my fingers around
You gonna watch oh, yeah like that
yeah I think I can probably
you can do it to yourself
if you can do it to yourself
that's literally the size of my dick
I know what that looks like
what? you know what that looks like
come on just hold on
maybe I don't know nothing
I hope you don't know I'm serious man like the
I thought your wings were wings but it looks like a bicep. Why do you have a
bison's fur like tight to your wall look at that he has a bison's like pelt
No, I think it looks cool. It looks like you're an Encino man
That's like a smiley head. Hey, man, you like I gotta go
Really want you to fucking do really cool, man
Okay, you're the best. What about me?
It was. That's what I'm saying.
He I give you the best man.
I don't need all this.
Please. I get it.
I get enough.
I get enough love from Justine.
I don't need it. Exactly.
Why don't you just say a little harder, you know, but you know, I can't.
You I know where you came from.
What? What? What?
Yeah, I came from my mother. Where'd you come from? Oh, you came from East Coast is what I'm saying
Yeah, and if you came to my domicile, I'd be box your fucking shit in
and I think you're a really cool cat and I hope you don't go man that's what I'm trying to say
and I'm telling the older brother
I hope somebody fucking smacks the shit out of you and exactly somebody can even
I'll pay somebody to slap the shit out of Ziggy. I got 20 bucks in my slapstick.
When I'm trying to, when I'm trying to be nice, I legitimately hope somebody
curts up to your fucking face and literally refakes your mouth.
Oh, one more time. He was to tell you you're his best friend to you.
Get ready for this. One time, I'm trying to be fucking nice.
Always up my ass.
Exactly, little snake tongue.
What?
What are you talking about?
Snake tongue.
I guess, that's what he's talking about.
You got a little slither tongue, like a little snake boy.
Amber, stop pretending like you have a life. Get up here.
Amber, I dreamt about you one day.
Later, boys.
Later.
Hey, who you call a boy?
Fuck off.
Who the fuck you call a boy? Fuck off.
The boy here. Nobody wants to hear it.
The fuck out of here.
Oh, you're my best friend.
You're my best friend.
Wait, Ziggy, get the fuck out of here.
You're a fucking hard R.
Get me out of here.
right now. Hard art. Well, you already said we're losers though, you're in your zone.
It's 3 o'clock in the morning. It's 3 a.m. for you fucking dorks.
I already never do the West Coast.
Yeah, you're three hours ahead.
You're it's three. It's five in the morning for you, right there.
And my name is fucking.
Oh, I tried to love you in a bad fire.
Don't make sports.
And I just that's all I bet you fucking do.
Like sports. I fucking yeah.
Oh, yeah, I thought you left 10 minutes. I love you guys. I love you guys. Ew. Why does he look like Jesus?
Actually, Amber says she has a great life. Does that look like a great life to you?
Amber, stop bragging about your fucking life. That's what Amber's house looks like. That
shit is crazy. That's not even a house. That's a shit. Don't get me started on you, Amber. I'm
stop making pictures. How do you
like like yeah I like this I like
this version of you. Thank you
that's actually the same shoes
you're presenting not no don't do
no gayship but you're presenting
some or at the moment you need to
just present that or all the time
exactly it was April fools and
the biggest pool I can think of
and maybe you know it helped you
when these old whores attack you,
and these old whores attack you.
Listen, I gotta give you,
I gotta spit some real shit to you right now, okay?
You gotta listen to this.
I don't know if you're gonna remember this.
But listen, you would get a lot more fucking love
and respect around here
if you stop trying to apologize to these old ladies
and just build your own.
You is right.
Nobody fucking likes them anyway. Go against them fuckers. Like it's not trying to be their friends. Fuck them. They obviously
Obviously just used you and dog pile you for content. Fuck them
Done. Yeah, talk to you about
About them they hate it. They fucking they cry about it make them cry
They they cry about you all day. Keep making
gun
They're not gonna make my boys psyche cry. We're gonna make them cry
Time to cry I'm not even I'm not even I'm not even trying to be like trolley or talk shit
Fucking go at them people there's a lot of people that don't fuck with them
That would rally behind motherfucker that you know goes against the grain of them
They don't know not everybody wants to be a part of their little fucking dorky gang
Yeah, I mean they're kind of like cruel and stuff and it's just like kind of like you know weird, but yeah
Well, they always attack you five on one. They always got to attack you multiple on one
They never could talk to you one-on-ones like you
And also Jesus called he wants his hair
When I tried to go up there earlier and talk my shit she got me blocked on stream yorker she can't
If you don't agree you're being
You come come like help me and back me up and like did whatever I say just fight and stuff like that
I ever ever said that to you one time in my life. I'm not this is like I'm actually looking at your nipples, but go ahead
So have I ever asked you to like come back me up or like I need I need to be backed up and
disagree with everything I say or anything like ever nope you never need to back up you you're
more you stand on your own you stand alone I stand alone God's back
I stand alone.
What else has gotten us faxing?
You do stand alone.
It's like, yeah, I respect you, man.
At least you stand alone.
I do.
It's me against the world, like my two-ball, you know?
Me against the world.
And you love it though.
You love it.
Hey, hey, I fit in my archetype just perfectly.
Yeah, but okay, but be the deserves to get porn bomb. I'm sorry. She does
She sits up there like and fucking sits on her little high horse
No, she deserves to get knocked down a little bit. Everybody does I love where be that tells people
Oh, don't you dare say that like be no you were drunk in like literally
I am like you when people talk about that. I'm like, oh, I'm sorry for poor bombing. I'm sorry for doing this
No, fuck you
Fuck them fuck these people as long as you got as long as you got people as long as you got people in your shit like
Jamie's Cowboys people that support your shit man. Fuck the other streamer. Oh, yeah, that's true
If you ever give in psyche, I would never respect you again if you ever give in
Play a song or sing whatever you want to do brother
Do what you gotta do buddy. So all I do is fucking sit around and row you up just to get you going so that they can talk shit
About it big. Oh, look at what's like you did. Look what's like. They're probably in the chat right now. Just watching
They're probably friends sitting here watching right now
Well, there's probably what like 50 or 60 viewers. I guarantee you
Your bag
This is actually a good song
I don't judge it till I hear it
Okay, you have to hear it. It's really good actually
It better be good. Hold on. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. It better be great
What the fuck? Damn it. If I don't go get more alcohol, I'm never gonna get it in
Do it, dude. Just go down. Go now, bro. There's dangerous out there
It's three in the morning for me, so you got time
I'm gonna go get one of them beatboxes, they're good
How are you excited to it? It's the best part when you dance to it
Hold, do not turn your head pilgrim The heiress thick with omens and hungry eyes
keep your heart beat steady as a drum in the underhaul
you ready for some hooker IRL you guys want to film some hookers film it
I mean I could possibly get killed but hey it's worth it right
hey content
I want to see what the prices are that's what I'm always curious about
There's no way it's 500, but there's no way it's like 200, it's gotta be somewhere in the middle, right?
Tell me man, I'll put you up for a drink.
Oh, you'll know.
I don't see anybody else as super fan of the chat. Thank you.
This is definitely like prime hooker time, too. It's not too late, but it's definitely not early
I feel dirty watching this song
In this life, there is no surrender
Is that a cactus?
Very nice.
It's a great song right here. It's a great song right here.
The itchy side suck you a little bit.
Come here my ginger.
Come to here my ginger.
My little ginger cat.
Don't talk to me like that. Yeah. Oh not you
This song is fucking awesome
It's so hard to see a fucking black cat when we have a brown carpet
It like blends in it's like camouflage or no seriously because she's black and brown
Memor day same like of a black cat crosses your path
She's not a black cat black and brown. I'm just saying you're black. You're a black cat
You're a trigger
Is this song still going wow, what an awesome nine-minute song
I know these a our songs are fucking long
I think I died and came back to life while this song was playing.
I think I turned 29, and I just turned 28.
And then I died again.
I died, came back to life, and then died again.
I think I died, came back to life as a gay man in Redondo Beach, then died again, then came back as me.
I love you psych, but I'm pretty sure I could see your heart beating through your ET skin. You're you have a body of ET
I love you buddy
But ET bone home, by the way
if you get ready to go out in the morning.
Psyche, you should be ET for Halloween
because you already have like his body.
So just like we're like an ET mask.
We'd be like, look at me.
Can you explain to me, like,
ET phone house.
Why everybody in your family,
including you, looks like the thing?
It's, oh my God, is that beta?
What the hell?
My picture is beta, yeah.
No, that's a bad picture. Come on. So this was like two or three years ago
And she accidentally turned her camera on on stream yard on war dogs panel. I forgot that. Oh my lord
I've seen beer. She's I think she's way this is before she ever cammed up like nobody really knew what she looked like for real
Like and she she did a cam slip and we got fucking got her ass
Do you know what I'd like to say to me to have this and thought
Be the let me lick this and that's not what she looks like. That's obviously AI. That's a horrible
Troll no, I'm not talking about the thing like the movie the thing I'm talking about the thing from the Fantastic Four
She's the baby talking about the thing like the dog
That's what amber looks like
Well, listen, you know what it's all fun and games, but don't talk about my baby amber like that. You understand me don't do it
Cuz I'm gonna say right now Q. I like you bro. What are you talking about Amber again like that?
I might have one of your little toys even though I think this is a dog toy
Oh my gosh, I can see your uh rib cage. I know you can I can see you're like, um breadbasket
You want to see it again here?
Amber you never watched the fantastic for the fuck
I love you. Yeah, you definitely have the same. I love you for the thing. Watch this real quick.
This, I swear you're like, I swear you're like this one.
Hold on. Kitty gang or kitty cakes.
Beat up much skinnier in face. Oh, you mean like that's like a fat face
Not gave you
With thunder stitched into her I've ever seen beat I'd spit right in her hair
You already did it the other way. Why would you?
Can you stop spitting on women too?
You know what's funny?
Bita makes fun of that chick that I spit on, but literally that chick looks like Bita.
Is the crazy one.
Can I hear my favorite song?
Please crank it up so I can crank it.
Thank you.
Listen at me. That's music right there.
She walks like honey poured in light
Don't be fuckin' nine minute A.I. songs, but please
She looks like honey poured
We were having a good panel
The heavens crumbling at her feet
Even angels fear her heat
She doesn't tend, she liberates
She doesn't break, she recreates
Her touch is profusely disguised
Her presence leaves the world revised
She murmurs where your beauty
Like a spell, the bravest and the cowards fell
Perfume thunder velvet storm
She's chaos wearing goddess form
The universe remakes the norm when ramp, how won't you hold?
Is this the Beals?
Amber said she can do the hard work.
You guys are fucking sick.
Q is a sweet boy, perfect person.
You're the perfect person, Q.
how does it feel to be perfect thank you for listening thank you for listening to that
thank you for listening i know it's long thank you for listening i'm sorry it's a little
bit long and amber do you want to come up and fart on the piano you can come up i'm
Come on up. I always want you. I'm always wanting you up here. Yeah, I threw up in my mouth a little bit too
Amber when it says sweet boy almost like puked a little bit my man like what the fuck
Well, it means, you know
18 and you know
I don't know
Is this the same song? Oh sweet page. No, it was two songs. It was two songs first was a no surrender that was rampa rampa
Yes, hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Oh, she's back. Hey, that's that's that's I guys. Let's put it on full screen
I can already see foolishness down the street.
You can't really see it on the camera, but where that bright light is, there is definitely
foolishness occurring.
Let me crack my beer.
That's a good thing about California, or especially this part of California.
You can basically do whatever the fuck you want around here as long as you're not committing any serious crimes
and nobody's gonna fuck with you because there's already serious crimes happening all around you.
This is a Wendy, sir.
Fuck you and your Wendy's.
Haven't ran into one person though. That's crazy. Usually at this time at night. It's fucking jumping out here
Where you going to get more beer fuck you bro be careful
I'm just going to get one more because I got a fucking work tomorrow. So
Get one tall can one more
That was probably what I was gonna do get a tall can call tonight well this place here
I don't think I don't know if they sell singles. I might just get a fucking a
beatbox or something
Get him a finger. I'll give you a nice buzz before you fall asleep
Shug it and if you get a nice buzz before you fall be coming on somebody said be careful, dude
I care about you my fucking gay. I mean is it good any gayer than that?
Whoever said that they definitely know how dangerous this place is that I live
No, I know you're careful too cute, but I'm not gonna sit there right be careful dude
I care about you like really
It was that Ziggy
It was nifty retard. Oh my god
That's what I'm saying. You know, that's the person has said that they're in Long Beach. That's what it's like around here
It's like I could you can walk down the street drink a beer do whatever like nobody's gonna bother you as long as you're just fucking
You go be a factor fool all you want
Nobody's gonna give a fuck as long as you're not fucking with nobody as long as you don't really fuck with the hookers when you start
Fucking with the hookers like and start like trolling them
Then
You can't you can't fuck with the hookers. You can like lightly you can talk to them and kind of you know
but you can't like really troll them hard because
The pimp literally happen to me on the screen the pimped up on me like the pimped up on me like in two seconds
He pulled up on on us like so quick
I was like it was like one second. I was talking shit to her and then the next second that dude was like there
a five-minute reality he had a quicker fucking reaction time than the police I
Would actually I would kill somebody they looked at the amber cross-eyed. That's my baby. Amber. You're talking about
Here you know flirty diamonds
Yeah, I know where the diamond of course. I know him. I know him. Oh
my gosh
You know the pimp runs out but the pimp has like a gun or something
But if you spray him in the face of pepper spray before he can get me got a gun
Oh effort
Hey guys, I saw Scribbles, if you know Scribbles,
Scribbles was like, can I see your butt to the,
the woman on Las Vegas?
The pimp ran out, Scribbles shot him in the face.
And he was like, ha!
Oh yeah, a little better.
I gotta be much with my little brother.
Did he really say, let me see your butt?
Well, there were, there were show girl costumes,
he was like filming their butt.
He's like, oh, turn around girls.
And they're like, get away from us.
And then the pimp ran out,
and he just shot him in the face of his mates in two seconds.
And then, then he ran away and the pimp was like, ha!
You're a funny. I love you brother. I love you sir. I love you too, Joe. Give me a hug.
There we go. Q's really cool. Yeah, you can joke a little with them, but then they don't like
film under their butt and stuff. That's like, that costs money. Oh, they got the game box.
Okay. They got the lemonade. What is it? Pick the punch or punch?
That's it. That's a good one.
Nice shadow. Why's your shadow
gay? That's why they're so close
to you. Oh, his is. Mine is too.
Mine actually like plays with my
butt. Hello there. Film that
hurtless bomb. What's up? Is
there a bomb? Film that bomb.
Would you say
I fuck with you bro wherever you are I do fuck with you
That was very kind that you did that the queue is awesome. Thank you queue. That was nice
Couldn't hear what the fuck you I it's crazy. You guys heard him before I could it cuz
I'm like trying to listen to him and I couldn't hear what he was saying
But then I heard Joe in the phone saying give him a fucking dollar
Was you walking Q I thought it was somebody else burn that's cool. You gave my dollar, bro
I fuck with you Q. I always will I fucking fuck with you. Thank you was I
Didn't fucking know
Did he have a sheep mask on?
He had a sheep mask on?
Oh, Jamie says.
You're the man, Q, for real.
Yeah, that was, Q, that was real.
Well, listen, I'm not trying to get all sad
and mopey or whatever, but listen,
I've been homeless before, and that shit fucking sucks.
Yeah, don't act like Siggi, don't get all gay like Siggi.
Especially at nighttime, it's not warm out here right now.
It's in like the 60s, which is cold for California.
Oh, this is an IRL for for these people out here is 60 mines will be like 45
No, I know and I know he has a heart. I know he has a heart
I know he has a heart because even when I look we don't make money up here
But Q gave is a gave some money to that man. So that right there. Come on. It's like
You're gay I would actually I would rob that guy and take your dollar from him
He had a shirt on that with the name tag said Jesus. It was like a mechanic shirt
You think you should think he did he does have a heart and even like when he does anything bad
He was like God forgive me like so you look if you if you look down the street right there. You can see them
What is it I see spotlights
Yeah, it's gonna be hard to see oh, yeah cuz the car was going but
Like I'm wearing basketball shorts
No underwear, I'm free ballin. Oh, I love that
What if you're walking back home and you're like can I get that dollar back like I'm really
I mean, Q, Q, this is a redemption arc.
I think this is a redemption arc.
I think Q is like gonna like turn it all around.
I really do, I really do.
He already is, he's turning it all around.
I like it, I like it a lot.
Okay.
Oh, don't get me started fucking Amber
with the fucking Jesus, Jesus.
Listen, listen, motherfucker.
The reason why Hispanic people are named Jesus
is because of the guy named Jesus.
Okay, not the other way around
When I was in Spanish class in sixth grade, they're like choose a Spanish name. My name is Jesus from moon
Hey, it's not a fucking it's not a it's not a Hispanic origin name
So they don't get to own the fucking rights of the pronunciation
And my real name John is actually the Jewish name as well. Yeah, it's like Juan. No, your name's Juan
That's Spanish, but it started as John or actually they didn't have a J until the 15th century
So as yeah, like they felt the Y it was yawn. Yeah, that means psyche one thing. I love about you, bro
I love when people like say like oh your name's John your name's John and one thing like when they say that about you
And you don't let her bother you and you just laugh it makes them even more mad or like
Oh, now I now you now I have to give you a blow job and you have to accept it. I love
Okay, we'll talk later. I love when you don't let it bother you and they get mad
I'm proud of my name. Okay. My name is John. Let's see if we can get some of the neighborhood cats to come out
They sometimes they do
You know I'm from I have the same name as the guy from psycho that that's enough of a clue, right?
If I came out here shaking the fucking bag of me I'll mix they would there would be like six of them running out
It's crazy at all. They'd all come out from the uh
When I came when I lost my cat out here like two weeks ago
I came out shaking the bag of food and they fucking came run and it was why all the cats except for my cat
Yeah, Paige can probably fix you but the thing is is like Paige has better like it's these people have better things to do than fix people
All right. Yeah, we don't have to fix it. We can't fix anything
But if we're going to be better people too, because then we are like less reactive and
then they're less reactive.
And it's like, if we can fix ourselves.
Oh, you're talking about some shit that Amber saying, oh, here we go.
Oh my God.
First of all, my interest, my interests do not lie in prairie page as much as I can
let this box empty.
Kim let's just box listen
No, your lasagna can't you be in there? Hey, she let the box. I should let the fucking box
Don't mind fuck Joe. What a mind fuck mind freak. Yeah, Chris Angel, right?
Yeah, Chris Angel that's one guy if you go back if you if you go back and watch that Chris Angel shit as an adult
It's hilarious
Remember when he cut a card out of somebody's head. He literally pulled a card out of somebody's skull
I can't believe I believe that shit as a child like no wonder kids believe in Santa Claus. I'll believe fucking
I believe in Santa Claus because I'm Christmas. I know you still call it Santa Claus
I believe in Santa what made you believe so you know for real tell me what you got what made you believe
Because yeah, this guy with a beer tried to break in my house on Christmas and I already asked for spoons
I gave him some cookies and he said thank you and he went up my that's when he realized you were gay
Yeah
Beard and man broke in the house like he was like, oh man, I kind of like this
You got Santa Claus high
Who is that guy with raccoon eyes up looking up
Hey, that's Peter. Don't be mean. Hey, turn it off. Yeah, that's Peter. Don't be meaner.
Come on. Oh my God. Oh my God.
That was an accident. Hold on. I'll go back on camera. I'm going to get in my cave. Does
anyone want to come warm me up? I'm so cold in this cave right here. Charles Manson peed
in this cave 40, like 65 years ago.
You did I still smell it. Oh, it's remember when Charles Manson with go boom parol and he'd be like
What what happened I want to show you something real quick Joe Joe show me some brother. I love he's like you
Watch this real quick. I don't think you've seen this yet.
Go ahead. Let me see it.
I'm pulling it up.
I hope it's the video of me and you making out.
I hope it's me and you making out.
I can't find that one, but I'm going to find that again.
But this is actually something that TripKick made.
All right, let me see it. Go ahead. Play it.
Yeah, it's coming up. Ready? Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Are you ready?
Okay, it's coming up right now. Watch this.
Watch this shit.
Got it. Okay. Ready? Ready? Ready? I was ready two seconds ago. Look at your seatbelt. Look at your seatbelt fucking what?
What's this the bars is saying that needed beat it and I tried to like track spiritually traffic her
Chose a house of random tight up the family at gunpoint
Go inside it's uncanny in a way. It's uncanny
Y'all there's, yeah, there's your, like, your spoilage, your little sisters, your little
Charles Bands and slaves.
Yeah.
You're doing exactly what I said.
I'm wondering, by and of members of a so-called religious cult.
Or at most for what?
Well, a leader, if they call Jesus, has had...
You people have done everything in the world to me.
Doesn't that give me equal rights?
I can do anything I want to you people at any time I want to, because that's what you've done to me.
You know, if I wanted to kill somebody, I'd take this book and beat you to death with it, and I wouldn't feel a thing.
It'd be just like walking to the drug store.
Do you feel a brain? Are you mad? Do you feel like Wooks and Bobbler representatives?
No, I know, but everyone told me, like, exactly what happened.
Yeah, you get me now?
Everyone told me, like, they were like,
okay, you're gonna be, she'll be calling you a trafficker, right?
Now I'm being called a spiritual trafficker.
Okay, that was, how was that?
Joe, are you smiling?
Uh-oh, it's me and Q.
Who's that pretty lady?
Hello?
Hello
You're the mystery
Yeah
Let me ask the mystery. Oh god. I didn't ask for all this
Relax psyche. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You want to sit up here alone?
No, please don't leave. Please don't leave calm your fucking tits. I
Calm down, please tits, please
Calm your tits. Where's my fucking shit, dude. I'm gonna pull my pants. I'm gonna pull my pants. I'm pulling them up, okay
Yeah, I didn't do anything I didn't do anything wrong
To me that that was chip kick that was funny amber amber
Hey, sure. I like I love trip kick. He's funny as fuck
Hey, yeah, I think we people do everything to me. I wanted to kill you
I can kill you over there with this kalimba right now, okay, and uh, hey, he's a he's a serial killer. He's a bad person
That's it. That's all I know
What the fuck are you talking about?
Charles Manson
Are you gonna get a are you gonna get a swastika tattooed on your fucking forehead next?
No, I need to pay for the BKG
Oh, yeah, so it's was a good next after that having on one donation for that yet
But it will look like kind of like this but well listen not enough people know about it yet
But they will there is a goal in the chat and I'm I will get a fuck BKG
Catch you. I'll have fuck put over it over the over Lenore like it will say fuck BKG
And it's like Lenore being angry defending me against these people
It is funny
And you have to go.
Charles Manson, I don't think he's a bad guy.
I think he wanted to get some pussy.
And then he's around all these entitled runaways
on acid and stuff.
And they went and did some bad shit
because they misunderstood his intention.
And he's like, what the fuck?
I didn't tell him to do this.
And then he went, I can just see myself.
If you guys were to do something like that,
and then they're like, well, cultists like you told me.
I didn't tell them to do that.
I was just trying to get some dick.
Yeah, it's real funny for you to say that I never got one that one suck not one suck on a dick
I never got one suck. It's real funny for you to say that now amber, but at one time you could never take a fucking joke
When you ever when you're getting high you can take a fucking joke at all
It's okay. You know, sometimes I didn't have a sense of humor
at one point, and I was like, oh, my God, B, no, no, no.
And now I can laugh at myself.
And because, you know what, maybe I am funny, clown, whatever.
I was like, Sweet Pea, stop making clips of me bald.
Now, I've seen worst said about me,
so whatever she said was a compliment at this point.
Yeah, so.
But she took all her clips down
because I made a list of, like, the people,
and I didn't put her on it.
What's the what's that?
Can you say one more time never mind never mind what would you say I want to answer it could just say one more time
No, cuz it was it was it was mean. It's okay. It was mean. It's okay. I don't care
You know you can say whatever you want to mean, you know, I don't know it wasn't mean about you
Okay, don't say anything about beta. Who's that? Who's that guy on this? It wasn't mean about beta either. Okay. Who's that on the screen?
That's amber
Who's that beautiful woman on the screen?
Yeah
Yeah, that's your beautiful woman right there
And there
Okay
She's beautiful. Oh, I was like a few seconds behind there was a beat a picture before this is she's beautiful. She's beautiful
Hey Amber, I'm not the one who arrested you. I'm not the one who committed the crimes. I didn't create this
Those mug shots
That's all you I mean, I I mean I saw like I saw like this video
But they're trying to get my dash cam footage shoe and I don't have it or not not that body cam footage
I don't have any body cam footage
Okay
Amber my mug shots are
Horrible there's no, are they worse than that though? Look at that one. Are they worse than that or I swear to God is worse
I swear to God is worse like much worse. Okay, and thank God in California. That's a face that misses Michael
Michael, look we see them on no Michael yon't
Okay, I don't know. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, you know what whatever. Wait, wait, wait. Can I wait? Wait, actually, you know what? I'm glad you brought that up because yeah
Not in a joking way like what the fuck did that that dude so he passed away, right? Like that's real or is that just a joke?
Yeah, no, he passed away. He passed away in July. So nobody knows why though or like what the fuck happened to him
He disappeared.
Scott says SUICIDE. Other people say that I think he had a heart problem or a congenital heart problem and stuff.
RIP Michael and Michael you were my he was my friend and it's like he always
no matter if he got kicked off the show or whatever he would sit backstage and I would like chat with
him backstage and stuff and he'd be like I love you psyche and his girlfriend wrote me the nicest
letter and she's like you know what Michael always said hey you know what let's go to psyches
because I like this guy and you know he's like you know goes through some bullying and stuff and
and let's go over their support him and stuff and so I guys I'm really lucky like and also you
Yeah, I know but we already talked about that. I know we talked about it
But yeah, but Danny passed away. I think March 9th or something
but I he was just in my chat like four days before and
I'm sorry if I said any wrong name. I'm sorry, but yeah, I like Michael or Michael and Danny and also, you know
other people passed away like
Who's the guy that Marty Marty passed away and but I've been told other people passed away that didn't and stuff, you know
So
Amber whoa amber. Why are you mad now?
I was literally saying those names when I was on panel with you on faded bones shit like a week or two ago
I was saying the same shit to you there. Why do you care now that it's that's like
Amber and raises a humor okay
Yeah, I'm saying same shit to her that I said to her like a couple weeks ago on faded bones panel
And she was having a laugh about it, but now she's like
I know Q's been through horrible bullying by some people.
I like slander and I know-
Oh no, I don't get bullied. I do the bullying.
I know, but this woman, this one woman, right?
Who likes you now?
But you, because you saved your life.
She says, because you were warned about some guy with a gun and stuff.
I was gonna do anything to her
Even whenever she was doing all that shit to me. I was laughing at her the whole time
I was doing
You're like kind of like an expert you're kind of like you're a king. I think I'm a king getting almost
I'm a baby. I'm a prince. I'm a gangster. You're gangster. Okay. You're a G. Oh, yeah
He's the OG. He's an OG Q is actually an OG of this of whole fucking IP to and stream reverse and all this stuff Q is like
been here like you know he's like people are like cute and and he's i'm now i'm honored over his
poor mom even his bigger bombs but i just i just saved those for myself to watch privately i delete
this rooms oh my god but you thought you were gonna get one there but you didn't i did i did
but you're like you would like it too much and i don't want to be clipped privately by you right
i won't finger bomb you
I know you guys come on good thing the thumb is the good thing the thumb is not considered a finger. You gotta say guys
Valley pop. Oh my god
My thumb really my thumb we're gonna can't we're gonna end the stream because of my thumb
Guys, I'll be I'm gonna restart the stream. I mean are you kidding me over the thumb? It's a thumb. It's okay
Jesus Christ. I have to save it privately in my I have to see it privately to watch later
Stop being a friggin stop being a weirdo if you have a stream. I'm not coming back